the halleyuda pascal triangle is a
triangular array of numbers built as
follows
every row begins with a one and ends
with a one
and every other entry in the triangle is
obtained by adding the two entries
directly above the entry in question we
can fill in the rest of the triangle
using this pattern
here we've only pictured up to row seven
in the halle utah pascal triangle
now let's go through this triangle and
shade only the odd entries
we get a picture that looks like this
but if we zoom out to show 256 rows of
pascal's triangle and shade only the odd
entries something amazing happens we
produce the sierpinski triangle
you